GWENDOLYN STRIPLING：你好。
GWENDOLYN STRIPLING: Hello.
欢迎来到生成式AI入门课程。
And welcome to Introduction to Generative AI.
我是Gwendolyn Stripling博士。
My name is Dr. Gwendolyn Stripling.
我是谷歌云的人工智能
And I am the artificial intelligence
技术课程开发者。
technical curriculum developer here at Google Cloud.
在这门课程中，您将学会定义生成式AI，
In this course, you learn to define generative AI,
解释生成式AI的工作原理，描述生成式AI模型
explain how generative AI works, describe generative AI model
类型，并描述生成式AI的应用。
types, and describe generative AI applications.
生成式AI是一种人工智能
Generative AI is a type of artificial intelligence
技术，可以生成各种类型的内容，
technology that can produce various types of content,
包括文本、图像、音频和合成数据。
including text, imagery, audio, and synthetic data.
但什么是人工智能？
But what is artificial intelligence?
嗯，既然我们要探讨
Well, since we are going to explore
生成式人工智能，
generative artificial intelligence,
那么让我们提供一些背景信息。
let's provide a bit of context.
所以两个非常常见的问题是
So two very common questions asked
什么是人工智能
are what is artificial intelligence
以及人工智能和机器
and what is the difference between AI and machine
学习之间的区别是什么。
learning.
可以这样认为，AI是一门学科，
One way to think about it is that AI is a discipline,
例如物理学。
like physics for example.
AI是计算机科学的一个分支
AI is a branch of computer science
它涉及到智能代理的创建，这些代理
that deals with the creation of intelligence agents, which
是可以推理、学习和自主行动的系统。
are systems that can reason, and learn, and act autonomously.
从本质上讲，AI与理论和方法有关
Essentially, AI has to do with the theory and methods
构建像人类一样思考和行动的机器。
to build machines that think and act like humans.
在这个学科中，我们有机器学习，
In this discipline, we have machine learning,
它是AI的一个子领域。
which is a subfield of AI.
这是一个从输入数据中训练模型的程序或系统。
It is a program or system that trains a model from input data.
经过训练的模型可以对
That trained model can make useful predictions
从未见过的新数据进行有用的预测，
from new or never before seen data
这些数据来自于用于训练模型的相同数据。
drawn from the same one used to train the model.
机器学习赋予计算机
Machine learning gives the computer
在没有明确编程的情况下学习的能力。
the ability to learn without explicit programming.
两种最常见的机器学习模型类别
Two of the most common classes of machine learning models
是无监督和有监督的ML模型。
are unsupervised and supervised ML models.
两者之间的关键区别
The key difference between the two
是有监督模型具有标签。
is that, with supervised models, we have labels.
带标签的数据是带有标签的数据，如名称、类型、
Labeled data is data that comes with a tag like a name, a type,
或数字。
or a number.
无标签数据是没有标签的数据。
Unlabeled data is data that comes with no tag.
这张图是一个例子，
This graph is an example of the problem
说明了有监督模型可能尝试解决的问题。
that a supervised model might try to solve.
例如，假设您是一家餐厅的老板。
For example, let's say you are the owner of a restaurant.
您拥有账单金额的历史数据
You have historical data of the bill amount
以及基于订单类型不同人给予的小费
and how much different people tipped based on order type
以及是自取还是送货上门。
and whether it was picked up or delivered.
在监督学习中，模型通过过去的例子学习
In supervised learning, the model learns from past examples
来预测未来的值，本例中是小费。
to predict future values, in this case tips.
所以在这里，模型使用总账单金额
So here the model uses the total bill amount
根据订单是自取还是送货上门来预测未来的小费金额。
to predict the future tip amount based on whether an order was picked up or delivered.
这是一个例子
This is an example of the problem
无监督模型可能尝试解决的问题。
that an unsupervised model might try to solve.
所以在这里你想看的是工龄和收入
So here you want to look at tenure and income
然后对员工进行分组或聚类
and then group or cluster employees
看看某个人是否在快速发展的道路上。
to see whether someone is on the fast track.
无监督问题都是关于发现的，
Unsupervised problems are all about discovery,
关于观察原始数据，看它是否自然地
about looking at the raw data and seeing if it naturally
分成几组。
falls into groups.
让我们更深入地用图形展示这些概念，
Let's get a little deeper and show this graphically
因为理解这些概念是
as understanding these concepts are
你理解生成式AI的基础。
the foundation for your understanding of generative AI.
在监督学习中，测试数据值或x
In supervised learning, testing data values or x
被输入到模型中。
are input into the model.
模型输出预测并将该预测
The model outputs a prediction and compares that prediction
与用于训练模型的训练数据进行比较。
to the training data used to train the model.
如果预测的测试数据值和实际训练数据值
If the predicted test data values and actual training data
相差很大，那就叫做误差。
values are far apart, that's called error.
模型试图减少这种误差，
And the model tries to reduce this error
直到预测值和实际值更接近为止。
until the predicted and actual values are closer together.
这是一个经典的优化问题。
This is a classic optimization problem.
现在我们已经探讨了
Now that we've explored the difference
人工智能和机器学习之间的区别，
between artificial intelligence and machine learning,
以及监督学习和无监督学习，
and supervised and unsupervised learning,
让我们简要探讨深度学习
let's briefly explore where deep learning
在机器学习方法中的位置。
fits as a subset of machine learning methods.
虽然机器学习是一个涵盖了
While machine learning is a broad field that
许多不同技术的广泛领域，
encompasses many different techniques,
深度学习是一种使用人工神经网络的机器学习类型，
deep learning is a type of machine learning that uses artificial neural networks,
使它们能够处理比机器学习更复杂的模式。
allowing them to process more complex patterns than machine learning.
人工神经网络受到人脑的启发。
Artificial neural networks are inspired by the human brain.
它们由许多相互连接的节点或神经元组成，
They are made up of many interconnected nodes or neurons
通过处理数据和进行预测来学习执行任务。
that can learn to perform tasks by processing data and making predictions.
深度学习模型通常具有许多层次
Deep learning models typically have many layers
的神经元，这使得它们能够学习
of neurons, which allows them to learn
比传统机器学习更复杂的模式
more complex patterns than traditional machine learning
模型。
models.
神经网络可以使用有标签和无标签的数据。
And neural networks can use both labeled and unlabeled data.
这被称为半监督学习。
This is called semi-supervised learning.
在半监督学习中，神经网络
In semi-supervised learning, a neural network
在少量有标签数据上进行训练
is trained on a small amount of labeled data
和大量无标签数据。
and a large amount of unlabeled data.
有标签数据帮助神经网络
The labeled data helps the neural network
学习任务的基本概念
to learn the basic concepts of the task
而无标签数据帮助神经网络
while the unlabeled data helps the neural network
概括到新的例子。
to generalize to new examples.
现在我们终于来到了生成式AI
Now we finally get to where generative AI
融入这个AI学科的地方。
fits into this AI discipline.
生成式AI是深度学习的一个子集，
Gen AI is a subset of deep learning, which
这意味着它使用人工神经网络，
means it uses artificial neural networks,
可以使用有监督、无监督和半监督方法
can process both labeled and unlabeled data using
处理标记和未标记的数据。
supervised, unsupervised, and semi-supervised methods.
大型语言模型也是深度学习的一个子集。
Large language models are also a subset of deep learning.
深度学习模型，或者一般的机器学习模型，
Deep learning models, or machine learning models in general,
可以分为两种类型，生成式和判别式。
can be divided into two types, generative and discriminative.
判别模型是一种类型的模型
A discriminative model is a type of model
用于对数据点进行分类或预测标签。
that is used to classify or predict labels for data points.
判别模型通常
Discriminative models are typically
在一个带标签的数据点的数据集上进行训练。
trained on a data set of labeled data points.
它们学习数据点的特征
And they learn the relationship between the features
和标签之间的关系。
of the data points and the labels.
一旦判别模型被训练好，
Once a discriminative model is trained,
它可以用来预测新数据点的标签。
it can be used to predict the label for new data points.
生成模型根据现有数据的概率分布生成新的数据实例
A generative model generates new data instances
基于学习到的概率分布。
based on a learned probability distribution of existing data.
因此生成模型会生成新内容。
Thus generative models generate new content.
以这个例子为例。
Take this example here.
判别模型学习条件概率
The discriminative model learns the conditional probability
分布或者y的概率，
distribution or the probability of y,
我们的输出，给定x，我们的输入，这是一只狗
our output, given x, our input, that this is a dog
并将其分类为狗而不是猫。
and classifies it as a dog and not a cat.
生成模型学习联合概率分布
The generative model learns the joint probability distribution
或者x和y的概率，并预测
or the probability of x and y and predicts
这是一只狗的条件概率
the conditional probability that this is a dog
然后可以生成一张狗的图片。
and can then generate a picture of a dog.
所以总结一下，生成模型
So to summarize, generative models
可以生成新的数据实例，而判别模型
can generate new data instances while discriminative models
在不同类型的数据实例之间进行区分。
discriminate between different kinds of data instances.
顶部图片展示了一个传统的机器
The top image shows a traditional machine
学习模型，试图学习
learning model which attempts to learn
数据与标签之间的关系，
the relationship between the data and the label,
或者你想要预测的内容。
or what you want to predict.
底部图片展示了一个生成性AI模型
The bottom image shows a generative AI model
试图学习内容上的模式，以便它
which attempts to learn patterns on content so that it
可以生成新的内容。
can generate new content.
区分什么是通用人工智能和什么不是的一个好方法
A good way to distinguish what is gen AI and what is not
就是通过这幅插图来展示。
is shown in this illustration.
当输出、或者y、或者标签是
It is not gen AI when the output, or y, or label is
一个数字或一个类别，例如垃圾邮件或非垃圾邮件，
a number or a class, for example spam or not spam,
或者一个概率时，它不是通用人工智能。
or a probability.
当输出是自然语言，如语音
It is gen AI when the output is natural language, like speech
或文本、图像或音频等时，它是通用人工智能。
or text, an image or audio, for example.
从数学角度来看，这样的可视化效果如下。
Visualizing this mathematically would look like this.
如果你已经有一段时间没有见过这个了，
If you haven't seen this for a while,
y 等于 f(x) 方程计算
the y is equal to f of x equation calculates
给定不同输入的过程的依赖输出。
the dependent output of a process given different inputs.
y 代表模型输出。
The y stands for the model output.
f 代表用于计算的函数。
The f embodies the function used in the calculation.
x 代表用于公式的输入或多个输入。
And the x represents the input or inputs used for the formula.
所以模型输出是所有输入的函数。
So the model output is a function of all the inputs.
如果 y 是一个数字，比如预测的销售额，
If the y is the number, like predicted sales,
那么它不是生成 AI。
it is not gen AI.
如果 y 是一个句子，比如定义销售额，
If y is a sentence, like define sales,
那么它是生成性的，因为问题会引发一个文本回应。
it is generative as the question would elicit a text response.
回应将基于所有大量的大数据
The response would be based on all the massive large data
模型已经接受过训练。
the model was already trained on.
总结一下高层次的传统、经典的
To summarize at a high level, the traditional, classical
监督和无监督学习过程
supervised and unsupervised learning process
采用训练代码和标签数据来构建模型。
takes training code and label data to build a model.
根据用例或问题，
Depending on the use case or problem,
模型可以给出预测。
the model can give you a prediction.
它可以对某物进行分类或聚类。
It can classify something or cluster something.
我们用这个例子来展示
We use this example to show you how much more robust
gen AI过程有多强大。
the gen AI process is.
gen AI过程可以采用训练代码、标签数据，
The gen AI process can take training code, label data,
以及所有数据类型的无标签数据
and unlabeled data of all data types
来构建基础模型。
and build a foundation model.
基础模型可以生成新的内容。
The foundation model can then generate new content.
例如，文本、代码、图像、音频、视频等。
For example, text, code, images, audio, video, et cetera.
我们已经从传统编程
We've come a long away from traditional programming
走到了神经网络和生成模型。
to neural networks to generative models.
在传统编程中，我们需要
In traditional programming, we used
硬编码区分猫的规则——
to have to hard code the rules for distinguishing a cat--
类型，动物；腿，四；耳朵，两个；毛发，有；
the type, animal; legs, four; ears, two; fur, yes;
喜欢纱线和猫薄荷。
likes yarn and catnip.
在神经网络的浪潮中，我们
In the wave of neural networks, we
可以给网络提供猫和狗的图片
could give the network pictures of cats and dogs
然后询问这是不是猫，它会预测出是猫。
and ask is this a cat and it would predict a cat.
在生成波中，我们作为用户
In the generative wave, we as users
可以生成我们自己的内容，无论是
can generate our own content, whether it
文本、图像、音频、视频等等，例如
be text, images, audio, video, et cetera, for example
像PaLM或Pathways语言模型这样的模型，
models like PaLM or Pathways Language Model,
或者LAMBDA，用于对话应用的语言模型，
or LAMBDA, Language Model for Dialogue Applications,
从互联网的多个来源中摄取非常非常大的数据
ingest very, very large data from the multiple sources across the internet and build foundation language
建立我们可以简单地通过提问来使用的基础语言
models we can use simply by asking a question,
模型，无论是将问题输入到提示中还是口头
whether typing it into a prompt or verbally
与提示本身进行对话。
talking into the prompt itself.
所以当你问它什么是猫时，它
So when you ask it what's a cat, it
可以告诉你它所了解的关于猫的一切。
can give you everything it has learned about a cat.
现在我们来到我们的正式定义。
Now we come to our formal definition.
什么是生成式AI？
What is generative AI?
生成式AI是一种人工智能类型
Gen AI is a type of artificial intelligence
根据它从现有内容中学到的知识
that creates new content based on what it has
创造新内容。
learned from existing content.
从现有内容中学习的过程
The process of learning from existing content
被称为训练，并在给定提示时产生
is called training and results in the creation
一个统计模型。
of a statistical model when given a prompt.
AI使用模型来预测预期响应可能是什么
AI uses the model to predict what an expected response might
从而生成新的内容。
be and this generates new content.
本质上，它学习了数据的基本结构
Essentially, it learns the underlying structure
然后可以生成
of the data and can then generate
与其训练数据相似的新样本。
new samples that are similar to the data it was trained on.
如前所述，生成性语言模型
As previously mentioned, a generative language model
可以从它所看到的示例中学到东西
can take what it has learned from the examples it's
然后根据这些信息创造出全新的东西
been shown and create something entirely new
基于这些信息。
based on that information.
大型语言模型是一种生成性AI
Large language models are one type of generative AI
因为它们生成了新颖的文本组合
since they generate novel combinations of text
以自然 sounding 语言的形式。
in the form of natural sounding language.
生成图像模型接受图像作为输入
A generative image model takes an image
可以输出文本、另一个图像或视频。
as input and can output text, another image, or video.
例如，在输出文本下，
For example, under the output text,
您可以获得视觉问题回答
you can get visual question answering
而在输出图像下，生成图像补全。
while under output image, an image completion is generated.
在输出视频下，生成动画。
And under output video, animation is generated.
生成语言模型以文本为输入
A generative language model takes text as input
可以输出更多文本、图像、音频或决策。
and can output more text, an image, audio, or decisions.
例如，在输出文本下，
For example, under the output text,
生成问题回答。
question answering is generated.
在输出图像下，生成了一个视频。
And under output image, a video is generated.
我们已经声明过，生成性语言模型通过训练数据学习
We've stated that generative language models learn
关于模式和语言的知识，
about patterns and language through training data,
然后，给定一些文本，它们预测接下来会发生什么。
then, given some text, they predict what comes next.
因此生成性语言模型是模式匹配系统。
Thus generative language models are pattern matching systems.
它们根据您提供的数据学习关于模式的知识。
They learn about patterns based on the data you provide.
这里有一个例子。
Here is an example.
基于它从训练数据中学到的东西，
Based on things it's learned from its training data,
它提供了如何完成这个句子的预测，
it offers predictions of how to complete this sentence,
我正在用花生酱和果冻做三明治。
I'm making a sandwich with peanut butter and jelly.
这里有一个使用Bard的相同示例，
Here is the same example using Bard,
它接受大量的文本数据训练，
which is trained on a massive amount of text data
能够与人类沟通并生成
and is able to communicate and generate
针对各种提示和问题的类人文本。
humanlike text in response to a wide range of prompts and questions.
这是另一个例子。
Here is another example.
生命的意义是--
The meaning of life is--
然后Bart给出一个上下文相关的答案，
and Bart gives you a contextual answer
接着展示最高概率的回应。
and then shows the highest probability response.
生成式AI的力量来自于使用变压器。
The power of generative AI comes from the use of transformers.
Transformers在2018年引发了自然语言处理的革命
Transformers produced a 2018 revolution in natural language processing.
在较高层次上，Transformers模型
At a high level, a transformer model
由编码器和解码器组成。
consists of an encoder and decoder.
编码器对输入序列进行编码
The encoder encodes the input sequence
并将其传递给解码器，解码器
and passes it to the decoder, which
学会如何解码表示
learns how to decode the representation
以完成相关任务。
for a relevant task.
在Transformers中，幻觉是
In transformers, hallucinations are words or phrases
由模型生成的单词或短语
that are generated by the model that
它们通常是无意义的或语法不正确的。
are often nonsensical or grammatically incorrect.
幻觉可能由多种因素引起，
Hallucinations can be caused by a number of factors,
包括模型没有接受足够的数据训练，
including the model is not trained on enough data,
或者模型接受了噪声或脏数据的训练，
or the model is trained on noisy or dirty data,
或者模型没有获得足够的上下文，
or the model is not given enough context,
或者模型没有获得足够的约束。
or the model is not given enough constraints.
幻觉对变压器可能是个问题，
Hallucinations can be a problem for transformers
因为它们可能使输出文本难以理解。
because they can make the output text difficult to understand.
它们还可能使模型更
They can also make the model more
容易产生错误或误导性的信息。
likely to generate incorrect or misleading information.
提示是一小段文本，
A prompt is a short piece of text
作为输入提供给大型语言模型。
that is given to the large language model as input.
并且它可以用于以多种方式控制模型的输出
And it can be used to control the output of the model
。
in a variety of ways.
提示设计是创建的过程
Prompt design is the process of creating
一个将产生所需输出的提示
a prompt that will generate the desired output
从一个大型语言模型。
from a large language model.
如前所述，gen AI很大程度上取决于
As previously mentioned, gen AI depends a lot
您输入的训练数据。
on the training data that you have fed into it.
它分析输入数据的模式和结构
And it analyzes the patterns and structures of the input data
从而学习。
and thus learns.
但是通过访问基于浏览器的提示，您，用户，
But with access to a browser based prompt, you, the user,
可以生成您自己的内容。
can generate your own content.
我们展示了基于数据的输入类型的示例。
We've shown illustrations of the types of input based upon data.
这里是相关的模型类型。
Here are the associated model types.
文本到文本。
Text-to-text.
文本到文本模型接受自然语言输入
Text-to-text models take a natural language input
并生成文本输出。
and produces a text output.
这些模型被训练来学习映射
These models are trained to learn the mapping
在一对文本之间，例如。
between a pair of text, e.g.
例如，从一种语言翻译成另一种语言。
for example, translation from one language to another.
文本到图像。
Text-to-image.
文本到图像模型在大量图像集上进行训练，
Text-to-image models are trained on a large set of images,
每个图像都配有简短的文本描述。
each captioned with a short text description.
扩散是实现这一目标的一种方法。
Diffusion is one method used to achieve this.
文本到视频和文本到3D。
Text-to-video and text-to-3D.
文本到视频模型旨在从文本输入生成视频表示
Text-to-video models aim to generate a video representation
从文本输入。
from text input.
输入文本可以是从单个句子
The input text can be anything from a single sentence
到完整的剧本。
to a full script.
输出是与输入文本相对应的视频。
And the output is a video that corresponds to the input text.
类似地，文本到3D模型生成
Similarly, text-to-3D models generate
与用户文本相对应的三维对象
three dimensional objects that correspond to a user's text
描述。
description.
例如，这可以用于游戏或其他3D世界。
For example, this can be used in games or other 3D worlds.
文本到任务。
Text-to-task.
文本到任务模型经过训练以执行明确定义的任务
Text-to-task models are trained to perform a defined task
或基于文本输入的操作。
or action based on text input.
这个任务可以是广泛的操作范围
This task can be a wide range of actions
例如回答问题、执行搜索、
such as answering a question, performing a search,
进行预测或采取某种行动。
making a prediction, or taking some sort of action.
例如，一个文本到任务模型
For example, a text-to-task model
可以被训练来导航Web UI或通过GUI对文档进行更改。
could be trained to navigate a web UI or make changes to a doc through the GUI.
基础模型是一个大型AI模型预先训练
A foundation model is a large AI model pre-trained
在大量数据上设计以适应或精细
on a vast quantity of data designed to be adapted or fine
调整到各种下游任务，
tuned to a wide range of downstream tasks,
如情感分析、图像标注和对象
such as sentiment analysis, image captioning, and object
识别。
recognition.
基础模型具有潜力
Foundation models have the potential
彻底改变许多行业，包括
to revolutionize many industries, including
医疗保健、金融和客户服务。
health care, finance, and customer service.
它们可以用来检测欺诈并提供
They can be used to detect fraud and provide
个性化客户支持。
personalized customer support.
Vertex AI 提供了一个模型花园，
Vertex AI offers a model garden that
其中包括基础模型。
includes foundation models.
语言基础模型包括
The language foundation models include
PaLM API 用于聊天和文本。
PaLM API for chat and text.
视觉基础模型包括稳定扩散，
The vision foundation models includes stable diffusion,
已被证明在根据文本描述生成
which has been shown to be effective at generating
高质量图像方面非常有效。
high quality images from text descriptions.
假设您有一个用例，
Let's say you have a use case where
您需要收集关于客户对您的产品或服务的
you need to gather sentiments about how your customers are
感受的情感。
feeling about your product or service.
您可以使用分类任务情感分析任务
You can use the classification task sentiment analysis task
就是为了这个目的的模型。
model for just that purpose.
那么，如果您需要进行占用分析呢？
And what if you needed to perform occupancy analytics?
有一个任务模型适用于您的用例。
There is a task model for your use case.
这里展示的是通用人工智能应用。
Shown here are gen AI applications.
让我们看一个代码生成的例子
Let's look at an example of code generation
在顶部代码下的第二个块中显示。
shown in the second block under code at the top.
在这个例子中，我输入了一个代码文件转换问题，
In this example, I've input a code file conversion problem,
从Python转换为JSON。
converting from Python to JSON.
我使用Bard。
I use Bard.
我在提示框中插入以下内容。
And I insert into the prompt box the following.
我有一个Pandas DataFrame，有两列，一列是文件名，
I have a Pandas DataFrame with two columns, one with the file
另一列是生成它的小时。
name and one with the hour in which it is generated.
我试图将其转换为JSON文件
I'm trying to convert this into a JSON file
以屏幕上显示的格式。
in the format shown onscreen.
巴德返回我需要执行此操作的步骤和代码片段。
Bard returns the steps I need to do this and the code snippet.
这里我的输出是JSON格式。
And here my output is in a JSON format.
它变得更好了。
It gets better.
我碰巧在使用谷歌的免费、基于浏览器的Jupyter
I happen to be using Google's free, browser-based Jupyter
笔记本，称为Colab。
Notebook, known as Colab.
我只需将Python代码导出到谷歌的Colab。
And I simply export the Python code to Google's Colab.
简而言之，Bart代码生成
To summarize, Bart code generation
可以帮助您调试源代码的行，
can help you debug your lines of source code,
逐行向您解释代码，
explain your code to you line by line,
为您的数据库编写SQL查询，
craft SQL queries for your database,
将代码从一种语言翻译成另一种语言，
translate code from one language to another,
并为源代码生成文档和教程。
and generate documentation and tutorials for source code.
生成AI工作室让您快速浏览和自定义
Generative AI Studio lets you quickly explore and customize
您可以在谷歌云中应用的生成AI模型
gen AI models that you can leverage in your applications
。
on Google Cloud.
生成性AI工作室帮助开发者创建和部署
Generative AI Studio helps developers create and deploy
Gen AI模型，提供各种工具和资源
Gen AI models by providing a variety of tools and resources
让您轻松入门。
that make it easy to get started.
例如，有一个预先训练模型的库。
For example, there's a library of pre-trained models.
有一个用于微调模型的工具。
There is a tool for fine tuning models.
有一个将模型部署到生产环境的工具。
There is a tool for deploying models to production.
还有一个供开发者社区论坛
And there is a community forum for developers
可以分享想法和协作。
to share ideas and collaborate.
生成性AI应用程序构建器让您
Generative AI App Builder lets you
无需编写任何代码即可创建生成性AI应用。
create gen AI apps without having to write any code.
Gen AI应用程序构建器具有拖放界面
Gen AI App Builder has a drag and drop interface
使设计和构建应用程序变得简单。
that makes it easy to design and build apps.
它有一个可视化编辑器，使得
It has a visual editor that makes
轻松创建和编辑应用程序内容。
it easy to create and edit app content.
它内置了一个搜索引擎，
It has a built-in search engine that
允许用户在应用程序内搜索信息。
allows users to search for information within the app.
并且它有一个会话式AI引擎
And it has a conversational AI Engine
帮助用户使用
that helps users to interact with the app using
自然语言与应用程序互动。
natural language.
您可以创建自己的数字助手、自定义搜索
You can create your own digital assistants, custom search
引擎、知识库、培训应用程序，
engines, knowledge bases, training applications,
以及更多。
and much more.
PaLM API允许您测试和实验
PaLM API lets you test and experiment
使用谷歌的大型语言模型和通用AI工具。
with Google's large language models and gen AI tools.
为了使原型设计更快速、更易于访问，
To make prototyping quick and more accessible,
开发者可以将PaLM API与Maker套件集成
developers can integrate PaLM API with Maker suite
并使用它通过图形用户
and use it to access the API using a graphical user
界面访问API。
interface.
该套件包括许多不同的工具，如模型
The suite includes a number of different tools such as a model
训练工具、模型部署工具和模型
training tool, a model deployment tool, and a model
监控工具。
monitoring tool.
模型训练工具帮助开发者使用不同的算法
The model training tool helps developers train ML models
在他们的数据上训练机器学习模型。
on their data using different algorithms.
模型部署工具帮助开发者部署机器学习模型
The model deployment tool helps developers deploy ML models
提供多种不同的部署选项。
to production with a number of different deployment options.
模型监控工具帮助开发者
The model monitoring tool helps developers
监控他们的机器学习模型在生产中的性能
monitor the performance of their ML models
使用仪表板和多种不同的指标。
in production using a dashboard and a number of different metrics.
感谢您收看我们的课程，介绍
Thank you for watching our course, Introduction
生成式人工智能。
to Generative AI.